This one is a longer note. I want to describe my whole day. I want to see how much time it takes to transcribe the whole thing.
I have to speak a little Hindi in between. I don't know how much issue there is about it.
Also, yeah, I started my day. I woke up. I made some breakfast for myself, put my eye drops because I had done my lasik surgery.
So I had to keep putting my eye drops. I keep calling them ear drops. They are not ear drops, they are eye drops.
I have four in the morning. Then I have one every two hours. Yeah, that's pretty much the whole plan.
Other than that, of course, I ate. Just wasted time.
I went to the gym around 11.30 and then worked. I had a leg day. It was brutal.
After the leg day, I just came back, took the one and a half hour train back so I had to only pay two per night.
Then came back, made lunch, had my protein shake and only laced around.
I did not do any work till 7 or 8 in the night when I was like, man, now I need to do something because the day is just about to get over.
But yeah, it's not been a very productive day, but that's fine because I'm not being asked to be productive for an hour.
So that's fine. Soon the day will be very different, but one good thing I look forward to is meeting people, working with them, discussing things.
Just by myself, I'm a complete loafer. We already know that there's nothing new about it.
But that's been pretty much my day. Pretty chill. I think much.
But yeah, this is a longer note, two minute note about just speaking about my day pretty much.